Magic and Illusion

BRIAN ROLE\`
============

Your Wonderment Is Brian's Business

Magic and Illusion

BRIAN ROLE\`
============

Your Wonderment Is Brian's Business

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

Creation: May 2018  
Latest Update: September 2018

Our Privacy Policy governs the privacy terms of our website, located at brianrole.com, the tools we provide you (the “Website” or the “Service”). Any capitalized terms not defined in our Privacy Policy, have the meaning as specified in our Terms of Use accessible at https://brianrole.com/terms-of-use/

Your Privacy  
Our Website follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.

Definitions  
Personal Data: Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).  
Usage Data: Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).  
Cookies: Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.  
Data Controller: Data Controller means a natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.  
Data Processors (or Service Providers): Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.  
Data Subject: Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.  
User: The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal

Data.  
Information Collection And Use  
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

Types of Data Collected

Personal Data  
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: Email address, Name, Phone, Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City, Cookies and Usage Data.

We may use your Personal Data to contact you such as but not limited to issues regarding booking requests and reservations, booking confirmation and payments and confirmed booking details and or updates regarding your booking or reservation. If you opt to subscribe to our mailing lists we may also contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of our mailing list receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

Usage Data  
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

Comments  
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Media  
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Tracking & Cookies Data  
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. Examples of Cookies we use: session cookies (we use these cookies to operate our Service) and preference cookies (we use these cookies to remember your preferences and various settings). If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Third Party Plugin and Software  
This Website makes use of third party plugins and software each of which have their own functions. These third-party plugin and software may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with our Website.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to the use of each individual third party plugin and software used on this Website.  We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Third Party Embedded Content   
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites(e.g Youtube, Google, Vimeo, Facebook etc.)  behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

How Long We Retain Information  
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information (except change the username). 

Use of Data  
We use the collected data for various purposes:  
To provide and maintain our Service  
To notify you about changes to our Service  
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so  
To provide customer support  
To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service  
To monitor the usage of our Service  
To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information.

Retention of Data  
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. We will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

Transfer Of Data  
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your our our state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy releases us from being held responsible for the misuse use of information by third-parties where this information is being stored.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Disclosure Of Data  
Business Transaction. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. Disclosure for Law Enforcement. Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

Security Of Data  
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)  
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), The Website legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

The Website may process your Personal Data because:

We need to perform a contract with you  
You have given us permission to do so  
The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights  
For payment processing purposes  
To comply with the law  
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)  
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. The Website aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:  
The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.  
The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.  
The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.  
The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.  
The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of your Personal Data in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.  
The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where the Website relied on your consent to process your personal information.  
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.  
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

Service Providers  
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Analytics  
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

Google Analytics  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Payments  
We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we mostly work with are:  
PayPal. Their Privacy Policy can be found on their website at https://www.paypal.com/privacy  
Revolut. Their Privacy Policy can be found on their website at https://www.revolut.com/privacy  
Stripe. Their Privacy Policy can be found on their website at https://www.stripe.com/privacy

Links To Other Sites  
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.  
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy  
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy  
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

If you are subscribed to our mailing lists, we will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by using the contact method we provided on our Contact page.

Share the magic

Copyright © 2006 - 2024 @ Brian Role\`

www.brianrole.com 

\-
